export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your thoughts when considering your weight and body image?",
      "options": [
        "Calm and rational+0",
        "Occasionally uneasy+1",
        "Frequently anxious, but actively working on self-acceptance+2",
        "Overwhelming concern, but actively seeking a positive body image+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Overwhelming concern, but actively seeking a positive body image"
    },
    {
      "question": "How often do you engage in behaviors to intentionally lose weight, such as extreme dieting or excessive exercise?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely or never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently, but exploring healthier approaches to weight management+2",
        "Always, as it triggers significant weight loss efforts+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently, but exploring healthier approaches to weight management"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you experience physical symptoms such as fatigue, weakness, or dizziness due to intentional weight loss efforts?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently, but actively seeking a balanced and sustainable approach+2",
        "Always during weight loss efforts+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently, but actively seeking a balanced and sustainable approach"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long have you been engaging in intentional weight loss behaviors?",
      "options": [
        "A short period+0",
        "Several months+1",
        "Years, but actively reevaluating and adjusting my approach+2",
        "I haven't engaged in intentional weight loss behaviors+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Years, but actively reevaluating and adjusting my approach"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with weight loss-related issues or eating disorders?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+0",
        "Considering it+1",
        "No, not yet, but open to seeking support+2",
        "No, and I don't plan to+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do these weight loss efforts impact your daily life, relationships, or activities?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact, but actively finding a balance+1",
        "High impact, but working on managing the impact+2",
        "Very high impact, but seeking support and healthier alternatives+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "High impact, but working on managing the impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your experiences of intentional weight loss behaviors?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes, but I appreciate their concern and support+2",
        "Frequently, and I'm grateful for their encouragement as I work on a healthier approach+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Sometimes, but I appreciate their concern and support"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing intentional weight loss behaviors is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+0",
        "Agree, and actively taking steps to address it+1",
        "Neutral, but open to exploring ways to improve+2",
        "Disagree+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Agree, and actively taking steps to address it"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the impact of intentional weight loss efforts on your mental and physical well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact, but actively working on improving my well-being+1",
        "High impact, but actively seeking support and positive changes+2",
        "Very high impact, and actively pursuing a holistic approach to well-being+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "High impact, but actively seeking support and positive changes"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the impact of intentional weight loss efforts on your mental and physical well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact, but actively working on improving my well-being+1",
        "High impact, but actively seeking support and positive changes+2",
        "Very high impact, and actively pursuing a holistic approach to well-being+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Very high impact, and actively pursuing a holistic approach to well-being"
    }
  ]
}
